Nguyen Hoang An - Software Engineer

Email: hoangan072024@gmail.com

Linked In: www.linkedin.com/in/hoangan-vn

Github: github.com/hoangan-vn Website: www.hoangan.online

Mobile: $+84\ 779672566$ Date of birth: 21/06/2002



EDUCATION

University of Information Technology - UIT

Information Technology; Senior; GPA: 7.64

Ho Chi Minh City Aug. 2020 – Aug. 2024

OVERVIEW

I have knowledge of Clean Code Principles and experience using Git to manage source code and participate in team projects throughout my academic journey. I have had opportunities to estimate project timelines, manage tasks using Trello, and write project documentation. Additionally, I have worked on cross-platform mobile applications using Flutter and developed web applications with TypeScript and ReactJS during academic projects and internships. I also have experience in server development with ExpressJS and NestJS to support these applications. In the future, I wanna become a software engineering expert and take on the position of Project Manager.

EXPERIENCE

Web developer
Viethas

Ho Chi Minh City
Feb. 2023 - Oct. 2023

Flutter developer

Golden Owl Solutions: Intern

Ho Chi Minh City
Dec. 2023 – Mar. 2024

Projects

Future $Fullstack\ developer$ 4 members $Mar\ 2023 - Jun\ 2023$

Github: github.com/hoangan-vn/future

- **Descriptions**: This is a website for selling decorations, where customers can find unique and beautiful items to decorate their homes. On the website, we offer a wide range of decorative accessories such as paintings, decorative lights, and much more.
- Features: View order list, Filter orders, View order details, Change order status, Manage products, Manage products, Manage accounts, Statistics, Login to dashboard, Logout from dashboard, Login, Register, Logout, View products, View product details, Search products, Manage addresses, Manage cart, Manage orders, Manage comments, Manage wishlist, Manage personal information.
- Technology: Typescript, ReactJs, Tailwind CSS, Redux, ExpressJs, MongoDB, Swagger.

Flutter intern project

1 members

Flutter developer Dec. 2023 – Mar. 2024

Github: github.com/hoangan-vn/flutter-intern

- **Descriptions**: This is a tracking application for pregnant mothers, looking up knowledge about taking care of their children from the time they are pregnant until their children grow up.
- Features: Sign In, Sign Up, Forgot Password, Manage Daily Quiz, Artical, Video management, Monitor the fetus,
 Take pregnancy care knowledge tests, Manage medication schedules, Search artical, video, Manage notifications,
 Multi language
- o **Technology**: Dart, Flutter, Firebase

Programming Skills

• Languages and Tools: Javascript, Typescript, SQL, NoSQL, Dart, NestJs, NodeJs, Prisma, React, React Native, TailwindCSS, Flutter, Firebase, MongoDB, MySQL.